<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Page xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Id>1</Id>
  <Title>Home Message</Title>
  <Content>&lt;h2&gt;Home Message&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome to EventServer!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;  &lt;p&gt;To edit this content, edit the blog page titled &amp;quot;Home Message&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;EventServer is a MicroCMS, meaning that it is an application that is designed to solve a very specific problem that contains some CMS functionality. EventServer is not a CMS whith complicated module and theme architectures. EventServer does however have parts of the site that can be updated without requiring the code to be modifed. Our focus on in-place administration has taken advantage of CMS like functionality to allow you to spend your time organizing the event, not creating a site for it. The Event Server project has a very narrow focus on the problem we are trying to solve without increasing the skills required to maintain or customize.   &lt;br /&gt;EventServer Features: &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Pages for Home, Speakers, Sessions, Sponsors, About &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;MicroCMS functionality allowing editing of static HTML content on any page using Live Writer or any MetaWebAPI compliant client. &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Built in Blog for announcements. &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Ability to post new announcements on the blog via Live Writer or any MetaWebLogAPI compliant client. &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Ability to future post announcements &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Allow potential speakers to Register and Submit session abstracts and bio information online &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Ability to review and approve or reject sessions (with comments that are sent to the speaker) &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Ability to assign sessions to a Track and TimeSlot &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Ability to manager sponsors, add/remove, edit, and assign to sponsorship level &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Ability to activate/inactive sponsors &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;100% CSS themes, no complicated theme engines.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</Content>
  <Description />
  <Keywords />
  <Parent>00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000</Parent>
  <HasParentPage>false</HasParentPage>
  <HasChildPages>false</HasChildPages>
  <Slug />
  <IsAuthenticated>false</IsAuthenticated>
  <IsPublished>true</IsPublished>
  <IsFrontPage>false</IsFrontPage>
  <ShowInList>true</ShowInList>
  <DateCreated>2011-03-18T11:12:18.2458904-05:00</DateCreated>
</Page>